I have some very good news for you about the Feral cat.
The Los Angeles Police Department is now employing Feral cats, who otherwise would have been euphemized at shelters, to fight rats and mice at two police stations; one at the southeastern branch and the other, the central branch.
And they report excellent success because once the mice and rats smell the presence of the cats, they flee.
The cats don't even have to chase them.
And it's said that at Parker Center, downtown LA, their main center, are now going to enjoy having the Feral cats drive out the rats there.
And you know, I think this should be carried out around the country.
Wherever there's a rat problem; whether it be police departments or elsewhere because the Feral cats do an excellent job and they would otherwise, I'm sorry to say, be euphemized.
Now, from South Korea, we have another case of cats that's very interesting.
They've just cloned glow-in-the-dark kitties.
Yes, they're giving them genes that make them glow in the dark when they're subjected to ultraviolet light.
Very cute, and of course, people want to buy them, they're Turkish Angoras.
The idea is that this research may actually lead to the cure of a human disease.
Right now, it's just a very cute idea.
And you know what I say to that?
Meow, Meow, Meow.